BRUNO LÓPEZ

Av 17 de Junio 461 Salta (Argentina)

+54 9 387 5430022

Email: <u>bruno.lopezcross@gmail.com</u> - <u>LinkedIn</u>

PROFILE

I am a software developer with over 10 years of experience in web development and related technologies. I have extended knowledge with object-oriented programming and databases, as well as the software development life cycle and its management. I consider my strengths to be creative, enthusiastic, and above all, self-taught spirit when faced challenges.

WORK EXPERIENCE

2020-Current

Backend Java Web Developer (Remote)

Right Partner and Sancor Salud SA, Santa Fe (Argentina).

Website: https://www.sancorsalud.com.ar

- Architecture and development application services with Restful architecture, integrating internal software projects with third-party projects
- Provided technical advice to the rest of the team regarding software tasks, needs, and issues.
- Tools
 - Java, Spring Framework, Springboot, SQL Server, Hibernate
 - o Git, Jboss, Openshift y Agile Methodologies

2019-2020

Fullstack Web Developer (Freelance)

Pharmacists Association of Salta (COFASAL), Salta (Argentina)

Website: https://www.cofasal.org.ar

- Provided architecture, development, and software direction services that could manage the control and billing of medicines sold by approximately 50 affiliated pharmacies to the institution.
- Trained professionals to work with new technologies demanded by the project.
- Tools
- Java, Spring Framework, Springboot, SQL Server, Hibernate, Git, Apache Tomcat, IIS
- o Javascript, Angular, Html5, Css3

2012-2020

Fullstack Web Developer .Net and Javascript

Instituto Provincial de Salud de Salta, Salta (Argentina)

Website: https://www.ipssalta.gov.ar

- Generated a web project that serves branches within the province, allowing its affiliates to pay for the various services provided by the institution.
- Maintained software and databases.
- Provided attention and consulting services to users of the web app developed.
- Tools
- o .Net, C#,SQL Server, Team Foundation, IIS
- o Javascript, Jquery, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap

2016-2017

Fullstack Web Developer

Integra Media & JBKnowledge, Salta (Argentina)

Website: https://smartbid.co

- Part of a team of over 10 people to maintain and update the software on bid construction this was one of the company's products, with clients mainly in the US.
- Tools
- o .Net, C#, SQL Server
- o Javascript, Jquery, HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap
- Internal JavaScript Framework

2015-2017

Teacher/Educator

Codesa Elementary School, Salta (Argentina)

- Provided introduction to programming and web design workshops for primary school children.
- Tools
 - HTML5, CSS3, Javascript y Scracht

EDUCATION

2019- current

Bachelor's Degree in Computer Science

University Siglo XXI, Salta (Argentina)

20015-2019

University Analyst in Information Systems

University Siglo XXI, Salta (Argentina)

2001-2006

High School Diploma Orientation in Project Formulation and Evaluation

Instituto de Enseñanza Media Dr. Arturo Oñativia, Salta (Argentina)

SKILLS

- Languages:
 - Spanish (native)
 - English Intermediate (Level 3 Language Center National University of Salta)

• Java, Spring ,Springboot Advanced

• JPA – Hibernate Advanced

• SQL Server Advanced

• JavaScript, Jquery , Angular Intermediate

HTML5 CSS3
Intermediate

• Git , Github Intermediate

Docker Intermediate